Constitution Collection 6035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Radio Assoc., American, 1949-1956 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Railroad Building Mechanics of America, Brotherhood of, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Railroad Brakemen, Brotherhood of, 1889 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Railroad Freight Handlers, Brotherhood of, 1904 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Railroad Operating Crafts, United, 1951-1954 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Railroad Patrolmen, Brotherhood of, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Railroad Signalmen of America, Brotherhood of, 1947-2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Railroad Station Employees & Clerks, Brotherhood of, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Railroad Telegraphers, Order of (AFL), 1895-1960 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Railroad Train Dispatchers of America, Order of, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Railroad Trainmen, Brotherhood of, 1884-1964 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Railroad Workers, American Federation of, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1925-1982 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Railroad Yardmasters of North America, 1925-1961 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Railway & Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Brotherhood of, 1919-1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Railway Carmen of America, Brotherhood of, 1913-1983 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of, 1910-1955 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Railway Conductors, 1899-1966 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Railway Expressmen, Brotherhood of, 1919 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Railway Mail Assoc., 1919-1949 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Railway Supervisors Assoc. Inc., Am., 1934-1953 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Railway Union, American, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Railway Yardmen of America, Order of (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Red Caps, International Brotherhood of, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Retail and Wholesale Employees, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Retail Clerks International Assoc., 1939-1967 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Retail Clerks International Protective Assoc., 1899-1955 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, CIO, 1939-1990 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Hospital and Health Care Local 1199, 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Assoc., United Slate, Tile & Composite, 1953-1983 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America, 1943-1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Rubber Workers of America, United, 1935-1944 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Sailors' Union, Lake, 1958-1960 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Salaried Unions, Federation of Westinghouse Independent, 1953-1971 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Salaried Unions, Independent, Federation of, 1949-1957 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1948-1981 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Seafarers' International Union, Atlantic and Gulf District, 1945-1989 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Seafarers' International Union of North American, AFL, Inland Boatmen's Union of the Pacific, 1948-2000 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Seafarers' Marine, Cooks & Stewards, National Union of, 1947-1970 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Seafarers' Marine, Firemen, Oilers, Watertenders & Wipers Assoc., Pacific Coast, 1919-1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Seafarers' Petroleum Workers, AFL-CIO, International Union of, 1963-1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Seafarers' Petroleum Workers, United, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Seafarers' International Union Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1948-1992 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Seamen's Union of America, International, 1911-1926 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Sergeants Benevolent Assoc., 1960-2000 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  1960, 2000
- Service Employees International Union, 1968-2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Service Station Employees Union, Western States, 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Sheet Metal Workers International Alliance, Amalgamated, 1915-1921 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Sheet Metal Workers International Assoc., 1937-2004 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Shoe Workers of America, United, 1913-1967 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, Brotherhood of, 1940-1957 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Shoe Workers' Protective Union, 1926-1960 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Shoe Workers' Union, Allied, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Shoe Workers' Union, Boot and, 1919-1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Shoe Workers of America, United, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Silkworkers Associated, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Sleeping Car Porters, Brotherhood of, 1936-1965 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Screen Actors' Guild, 1994-1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Service Employees International Union, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Spinners Union of America, International, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Staff Officers' Assoc., 1961-1964 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Stage Employees, International Alliance of Theatrical, 1913-2005 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, American Federation of, 1938-2005 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- State, County & Municipal Workers of America, 1941-1943 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Steam Shovelmen, Associated Union of, 1914 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Steam Shovel and Dredge Men, International Brotherhood of, 1919 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Steelworkers of America, United, 1942-2008 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers Organizing Committee, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Stereotypers and Electrotypers International Union of North America, 1904-1925 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Stereotypers and Electrotypers Union, International, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Stereotypers and Electrotypers International Union of North America, 1926-1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, 1941-1967 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Stonecutters Assoc. and Journeymen, 1898-1929 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Stove, Furnace and Allied Appliance Workers, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Stove Mounters & Stove Processors International Union, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Stove Mounters International Union of North America, 1926-1960 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Street and Electric Railway Employees of America, Amalgamated Assoc., 1913-1929 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Amalgamated Assoc., 1935-1949 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Street Railway Employees of America, 1892 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Sugar Workers and Allied Industries Unions, 1947-1958 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Switchmen's Union of North America, 1900-1967 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Table Knife Grinders' National Union of the United States, 1902 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Tailors Union of America, Journeymen, 1898-1921 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Teachers, American Federation of, 1962-1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Teachers, Local, 1943-1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Teachers, New York Congress of, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, International Brotherhood of, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Tool Craftsmen, International Assoc. of, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Teachers, New York State United, 1974-1981 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, International Brotherhood of, 1916-2001 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Technical Engineers, American Federation, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Technical Engineers, American Federation of, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Technical Engineers, International Federation of Professional and, 2000-2009 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Telecommunications International Union, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Telegraph Workers, United, 1971-1983 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Telegraphers, Brotherhood of, 1890 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Telegraphers Union of America, Commercial, 1914-1967 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Telephone Organizations United, 1953-1971 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Telephone Unions, Alliance of Independent, 1966-1970 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Telephone Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1923-1929 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1960-1982 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Textile Operatives, American Federation of, 1922-1927 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Textile Processors, Service Trades, Health Care, Professional Technical Employees International Union, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Textile Union of America, Independent, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers of America, Amalgamated, 1922 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Textile Workers of America, United, 1936-1992 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers Progressive Union, 1887 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Textile Workers Union of America, 1941-1972 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Tile, Marble, Terrazzo, Finishers, Shop Workers & Granite Cutters International Union, 1978-1984 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Timberworkers, International Union of, 1920 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Tobacco Workers, International Union, 1905-1976 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Tool and Diemakers Assoc. (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Tool Craftsmen, International Assoc. of, 1953-1970 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Train Dispatchers Assoc., American, 1927-1967 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Transit Employees, International, 1927 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Transit Supervisors Organization, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Transit Union, Amalgamated, 1967-1986 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Transport Workers Union of America, 1957-2005 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Transportation, Communication Employees Union, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Transportation, Communication International Union, 1987-2004 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Transportation Union, United, 1969-2007 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Transportation Union, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, United, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Travelers' Goods & Leather Novelty Workers' International Union of America, 1912 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Treasury Employees Union, National, 1967-1991 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Truck Drivers, Chicago, Local 705, 1954-1966 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Tugmen's and Pilots' Protective Assoc., 1959 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Tunnel & Subway Constructors International Union of North America, 1910 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Typographical Union, International, 1898-1919 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Typographical Union, International, 1920-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Typographical Union, International, 1950-1970 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Typographical Union, International, 1971-2000 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Typographical Union, Locals, 1934-1988 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- United Assoc. of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- United Auto Workers, 1977-1984 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, 1974-1995 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  1974, 1995
- United Federation of Labor, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- United Labor League, Philadelphia, 1893 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- United Mine Workers of America, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Assoc., 1927 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- United Storeworkers, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- United Transportation Union, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- University Employees, Federation of, 1950-1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- University Professors, American Assoc. of, 1977-1985 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- University Professions, United, 1998-2007 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Upholsterers International Union of North America, 1946-1982 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Utility Workers Union of America, 1950-2003 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Wall Paper Craftsmen, United, 1923-1938 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Watch Workers Union, 1944 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Watchmen's Assoc., Independent, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Weavers' Protective Assoc., Power Loom Ingrain Carpet, 1894 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Welders, Assoc. of Certified, 1934 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1938-1946 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Window Glass Cutters League of America, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Wire Weavers, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Women's Trade Union League, National, 1926 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers' Union, 1929-1976 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  1929, 1976
- Woodcarvers Assoc. of North America, International, 1908-1914 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Woodsmen & Sawmill Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Woodworkers of America, International, 1945-1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Workers International Independent Union, 1917 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Workmen's Circle, the, 1952-1978 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Writers' Guild of America, East Inc., 1957-1980 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Writers' Guild of America, West Inc., 1955-1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Yardmen's Assoc., Chicago, 1920 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers, International Bortherhood of, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Letter Carriers, National Association of, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Lithographers of America, Amalgamated, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Locomotive Engineers, Grand International Brotherhood of, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of, 1948-1963 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, International, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of, 1949-1980 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Maritime Union of America, National, 1947-1963 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Molders and Foundry Workers, International, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Newspaper Guild, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Post Office Clerks, National Federation of, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Post Office Clerks, United National Association of, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America, International, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, International Brotherhood of, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Railroad Operating Crafts, United, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Railroad Trainmen, Brotherhood of, 1950-1964 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Railway Carmen of America, Brotherhood, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Railway Conductors and Brakemen, Order of, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Railway Conductors, Order of, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Retail Clerks International Association, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1953-1957 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Sleeping Car Porters, Train, Chair Car, Coach Porters and Attendants, Brotherhood of, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Amalgamated Association of, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Switchmen's Union of North American, 1963-1967 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, International Brotherhood of, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, International Alliance of, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Transport Workers Union of America, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1970-1989 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- United Tranportation Union, 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 34)
- Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, Federation of, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- By-Laws and Rules of Court Friendship. Federated Freemen of America, 1934 (Box 63, Folder 36)
- AFL-CIO; Agricultural Workers Union; Air Line Pilots Association; ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America); Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1952-1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Government Employees; AFSCME (American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees); UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workes of America), 1952-1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers; Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers; Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers; BSEIU (Building Service Employees' International Union), 1950-1970 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Carpenters and Joiners; Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers; Chemical Workers; CSEA (Civil Service Employees Association); Commercial Telegraphers; Construction Workers, 1950-1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- UE (United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America) and IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), 1951- 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Fire Fighters; Foremen's Association; Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers; Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders; ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union); Life Insurance Agents, 1949-1952 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- IAM (International Association of Machinists); Marine and Shipbuilding Workers; UMW (United Mine Workers of America), 1946- 1973 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- AFM (American Federation of Musicians); Oil Workers; Operating Engineers; Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers; Photo-Engravers, 1950- 1972 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers; Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers; Journeymen Steamfitters and Apprentices; Technical Engineers; TWUA; Upholsterers; Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers, 1951-1977 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1955-1957 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Grain Elevator Employees, Local 1286. International Longshoremen's Association, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Actors; Air Line Pilots Association; Air Line Stewards and Stewardessess Association; Aluminum Workers; UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workes of America), 1939-1962 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers; Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmotologists and Proprietors; Blacksmiths and Helpers; Boiler Makers, Iron Ship Builders and Helpers, 1905-1966 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Boot and Shoe Workers; Brick and Clay Workers; Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers; Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers; Building Trades Department; Building and Construction Trades Department, 1906-1964 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- California State Federation of Labor; Canadian Congress of Labor; Carpenters and Joiners; Chemical Workers Union, 1890-1958 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Communication Workers; United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, 1940-1967 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- American Flint Glass Workers; Glass Bottle Blowers; Glass and Ceramic Workers; Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers; Hosiery Workers; Iron, Steel and Tin Workers, 1912-1956 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Journeymen Tailors; Laundry, Dry Cleaning & Dye House Workers; Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union; Amalgamated Lithographers, 1900-1962 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1918-1936 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1956-1971 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- American Federation of Musicians; Maritime Union; Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen; Metal Trades Department; Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1920-1961 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- International Association of Machinists and American Newspaper Guild, 1916-1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- American Newspaper Guild; Oil Workers International Union (CIO); and Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1920-1967 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America and International Photo-Engravers' Union of North America, 1922- 1951 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- International Photo-Engravers' Union of North America and United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1943-1964 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union of North America and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1907-1954 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO and Retail Clerks International Protective Association, 1918-1864 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Unon, 1902-1924 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Teachers; Technical Engineers', Architects' and Draftsmen's Unions; Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators; Tobacco Workers; Union Label and Trades Department; Industrial Union Department; Upholsterers; Utility Workers, 1922-1967 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers' Union, 1908-1967 (Box 65, Folder 9)